<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>alexander alexandrowitz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:32879/</link>
    <description>Recent content on alexander alexandrowitz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <copyright>© alexquadrat</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:32879/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://localhost:32879/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:32879/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Alexander Alexandrowitz and i was born in Aachen in 1989. I am a Cloud Engineer and former Software developer with great interest in automation, Python, smart home and music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>imprint/privacy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:32879/imprint-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:32879/imprint-privacy/</guid>
      <description>Datenschutzerklärung Verantwortlicher Alexander Alexandrowitz&#xA;Lilienweg 5&#xA;52457 Aldenhoven&#xA;info[at]alexandrowitz.de&#xA;Arten der verarbeiteten Daten Bestandsdaten (z.B., Personen-Stammdaten, Namen oder Adressen). Kontaktdaten (z.B., E-Mail, Telefonnummern). Inhaltsdaten (z.B., Texteingaben, Fotografien, Videos). Nutzungsdaten (z.B., besuchte Webseiten, Interesse an Inhalten, Zugriffszeiten). Meta-/Kommunikationsdaten (z.B., Geräte-Informationen, IP-Adressen). Kategorien betroffener Personen Besucher und Nutzer des Onlineangebotes (Nachfolgend bezeichnen wir die betroffenen Personen zusammenfassend auch als „Nutzer“).&#xA;Zweck der Verarbeitung Zurverfügungstellung des Onlineangebotes, seiner Funktionen und Inhalte. Beantwortung von Kontaktanfragen und Kommunikation mit Nutzern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use your heatpump efficiently with sun energy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:32879/posts/heatpump-sun-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:32879/posts/heatpump-sun-energy/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites up-to-date Home Assistant installation photovoltaic system which sends production data to Home Assistant heat pump which can be controlled by Home Assistant a helper variable (type bool) which indicates photovoltaic electricity surplus an integration to get remaining photovoltaic production of the day (Forecast Solar integration) important: I have a Viessmann heat pump (vitocal 200a), which might work different than yours I&amp;rsquo;m afraid you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to use this Automation as Ctrl+C; Ctrl+V with your setup, but at least you will have a good starting point.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
